Athletics, Department of; Records ua746
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Photographs, 9; 14.86 cubic ft.
  - Men's Basketball Team, Undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball, Will Brand, Undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Men's Football and women's Soccer, Undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Men's Lacrosse, Undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Milt Richards with ESPN, Negative and Slide, Undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Morrison Teague Negatives, Undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - NACDA Event, H. Carl McCall, Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - New York Giants, Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - New York Giants Photographs by Mike Totaro, Undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Printing Company Negatives, Undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Sal Cintorino, Head Football Coach, Central Connecticut State University, Undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Soccer, Nick Southworth, Undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Staff Headshot Negatives, Undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Ted Fossick of the Milne School, Undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Tennis Coach Joe Trepasso, Undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - UAlbany Field, Undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - UAlbany President Dr. Karen R. Hitchcock, Undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Unidentified Female Swimmer, Undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Unidentified Football Player, Undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Unidentified Male Basketball Player, Undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - University at Albany president Vincent O'Leary, Undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Volleyball, Undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Women's Basketball, Undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Women's Basketball Team, Undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Women's Basketball Team, Undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Women's Lacrosse, Undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Soccer Scorebooks, 1967-1983; 1 cubic ft.
  This series contains University at Albany men's soccer scorebooks from 1967 to 1983.
- Objects, ca. 1960-1990; 10; 5 cubic ft.
  The series is unprocessed and is likely disorganized. Individual items may be difficult to find.
  Contains athletics memorobilia
- UAlbanySports.com, 1
  URL
  http://www.ualbanysports.com/
  Web Collection